[
    {
        "category": null, 
        "type": "Multiple Choice", 
        "difficulty": null, 
        "question": "How many playable characters are there in the game?", 
        "correct_answer": "25",
        "answers": [
            "5",
            "12",
            "25",
            "18"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": null, 
        "type": "Multiple Choice", 
        "difficulty": null, 
        "question": "How many total hours of vs battles does a single player need to unlock Mewtwo", 
        "correct_answer": "4",
        "answers": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "4",
            "5"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": null, 
        "type": "Multiple Choice", 
        "difficulty": null, 
        "question": "How many characters in total are represented on the Melee roster from the Pok√©mon franchise?", 
        "correct_answer": "20",
        "answers": [
            "5",
            "10",
            "20",
            "50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": null, 
        "type": "Multiple Choice", 
        "difficulty": null, 
        "question": "In which stage do you fight the Wire Frames?", 
        "correct_answer": "Battlefield",
        "answers": [
            "Great Bay",
            "Final Destination",
            "Battlefield",
            "Fourside"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": null, 
        "type": "Multiple Choice", 
        "difficulty": null, 
        "question": "Which of these stages is not a Past Stage in Super Smash Bros. Melee?", 
        "correct_answer": "Hyrule Temple",
        "answers": [
            "Dream Land",
            "Hyrule Temple",
            "Yoshi's Island",
            "Kongo Jungle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": null, 
        "type": "Multiple Choice", 
        "difficulty": null, 
        "question": "Which trophy requires data from another game in order to unlock it?", 
        "correct_answer": "Captain Olimar",
        "answers": [
            "Tom Nook",
            "Alpha",
            "Mr. Resetti",
            "Captain Olimar"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": null, 
        "type": "Multiple Choice", 
        "difficulty": null, 
        "question": "Who is the only character from Smash 64 to not show up in the Melee intro video?", 
        "correct_answer": "Luigi",
        "answers": [
            "Fox",
            "Luigi",
            "Jigglypuff",
            "Captain Falcon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": null, 
        "type": "Multiple Choice", 
        "difficulty": null, 
        "question": "Which character cannot charge their down smash when too close to the ledge?", 
        "correct_answer": "Ness",
        "answers": [
            "Ness",
            "Samus",
            "Roy",
            "Bowser"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": null, 
        "type": "Multiple Choice", 
        "difficulty": null, 
        "question": "In 'Adventure Mode' (normal difficulty), who do you have to beat on the level 'Final Destination'?", 
        "correct_answer": "Giga Bowser",
        "answers": [
            "Master Hand",
            "Giga Bowser",
            "Marth",
            "Mewtwo"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": null, 
        "type": "Multiple Choice", 
        "difficulty": null, 
        "question": "How many 'Recover Hearts' do you get in 'All Star Mode'?", 
        "correct_answer": "3",
        "answers": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "6"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "category": null, 
        "type": "True/False", 
        "difficulty": null, 
        "question": "Prior to the release of Super Smash Bros. Melee, no game in Nintendo's Fire Emblem series had ever received an official North American release.", 
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "category": null, 
        "type": "True/False", 
        "difficulty": null, 
        "question": "Super Smash Bros. Melee is the first game in the Super Smash Bros. series to be rated T (Teen).", 
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": null, 
        "type": "Guess That Player", 
        "difficulty": null,
        "stop": 12, 
        "youtube_id": "-x1xVkWR73U",
        "question": "Which captain Falcon Player is playing?", 
        "correct_answer": "Wizzrobe",
        "answers": [
            "S2J",
            "n0ne",
            "Wizzrobe",
            "SquidTheCat"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": null, 
        "type": "Guess That Player", 
        "difficulty": null,
        "stop": 18, 
        "youtube_id": "ctYqblrnylw",
        "question": "Which Falco Player is playing?", 
        "correct_answer": "n0ne",
        "answers": [
            "Mang0",
            "Ginger",
            "n0ne",
            "Squid"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": null, 
        "type": "Guess That Player", 
        "difficulty": null,
        "stop": 29, 
        "youtube_id": "aCCf-nDAtJg",
        "question": "Which (grey) Falcon Player is playing?", 
        "correct_answer": "Lord",
        "answers": [
            "S2J",
            "Jeapie",
            "Gahtzu",
            "Lord"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": null, 
        "type": "Guess That Player", 
        "difficulty": null,
        "stop": 16, 
        "youtube_id": "vrOdzYh8OL4",
        "question": "Which Marth Player is playing?", 
        "correct_answer": "Zain",
        "answers": [
            "KoDoRiN",
            "Zain",
            "Mew2King",
            "Fendrick Lamar"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": null, 
        "type": "Guess That Player", 
        "difficulty": null,
        "stop": 18, 
        "youtube_id": "D60WKVgRb64",
        "question": "Which Luigi Player is playing?", 
        "correct_answer": "Eddie Mexico",
        "answers": [
            "Abate",
            "Ilovebagelz",
            "LuigiKid",
            "Eddie Mexico"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": null, 
        "type": "Guess That Player", 
        "difficulty": null,
        "stop": 23, 
        "youtube_id": "EAJU_5QhHrA",
        "question": "Which Fox Player is playing?", 
        "correct_answer": "Crush",
        "answers": [
            "Hax$",
            "Mang0",
            "Crush",
            "Moky"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": null, 
        "type": "Guess That Player", 
        "difficulty": null,
        "stop": 16, 
        "youtube_id": "cMYcEIMvEm4",
        "question": "Which Link Player is playing?", 
        "correct_answer": "Savestate",
        "answers": [
            "Savestate",
            "Axe",
            "Aether",
            "Tang"
        ]
    }
] 